<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollingText</string>
    <string name="article_title">Android OS</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Dalvik Bytecodes</string>
    <string name="article_text">With the rise of heterogeneous systems,
        there is a requirement for a scalable software system that is
        cost-effective and maintenance-free. Virtual machines (VMs)
        provide abstraction from the heterogeneity, and present a
        low-cost, scalable software development environment, as in the
        case of VM-based modern programming languages like Java.In this
        article, we will cover the fundamental concepts of a VM,
        using one of the critical components of Google’s Android OS —
        the Dalvik VM (https://davanum.wordpress.com/).

        A virtual machine (or VM) is an isolated, self-contained
        implementation that abstracts hardware resources. Typically,
        it simulates an actual physical machine capable of executing
        instruction sets. Broadly, VMs are classified based on how they
        work and their  functionality. There are process VMs, which
        support the execution of a single process/program (e.g., Java,
        .NET), and system VMs, which support execution of a complete
        operating system (e.g., VirtualBox, VMWare).

        In general, a VM is an interpreter for an instruction-set.
        The fundamental task of a compute machine is to carry out an operation.
        An operation is performed with the execution of a set of instructions.
        A basic instruction goes through the following cycle of events:

        - Instruction fetch, where an instruction is fetched from memory.
        - Decoding, which determines the type of the instruction — the
          opcode, or the operation it is supposed to perform. Additionally,
          decoding may also involve fetching operand(s) from memory.
        -Execute. The decoded instruction is then executed; the operation
        is performed on the operands. Storing the result in the mentioned
        register.
    </string>

</resources>
